warseer.com 2010-06-23

# Privacy Statement - WarSeer

|   | 

## Privacy Statement

nick  12/04/2006 - 08:19   

Privacy Statement for WarSeer

WarSeer has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.  
The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website:  

WarSeer (www.warseer.com)  

WarSeer understands the importance of maintaining the privacy of any and all of its visitors. Therefore, WarSeer only collects information that you willingly provide, and does not pass this on to any third party without prior consent. WarSeer may occasionally set browser cookies, but these are only used to improve service and do not collect any personal information. Personal information includes; your name, email address, street address, age, interests and opinions. WarSeer reserves the right to contact users regarding personal information they have submitted should the need arise.   

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your computer also stores your WarSeer Forum username and password in the form of a cookie to simplify usage of the forums.  

This site contains links to other sites. WarSeer is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.   

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Access to all data is resricted and only select individuals may alter parts of the site, including the Brushworks and the columns (updated by numerous people). Only the webmaster (Nicholas Blumire) and server administrators may alter any of the data on the server. Nightly backups are also made of all data.  

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

1.By changing their profile  

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us using the feedback page which can be found [here](http://www.warseer.com/forums/sendmessage.php?s=f581516216f26c4a576ad3e6ba934e14).  

Nicholas Blumire,   
WarSeer Webmaster
